Leach, W. Barton (Walter Barton), 1900 -1971. Papers, 1920-1971: Finding Aid.
Papers, 1920-1971.
- CONTINGENT I
  - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE (UNBOUND)
    - F-Miscellany (alphabetical), 3-6 to 3-7
      - 3-7, Fordyce, C. Powell 1960-1966 Fortas, Abe 1968-1969 Foster, John S., Jr. 1969 French, Peter 1961 Freund, Paul A. 1968-1971 Fuchsberg, Jacob D. 1968 Fuller, Lon L. 1971
    - Gavin, James M. (General) 1961, 3-8
    - Gerhart, Eugene C. 1968, 3-9
    - Gibbs, Norman H. (Professor) 1955-1966, 3-10
    - Gilpatric, Roswell (Deputy Secretary of Defense) 1960-1964, 3-11
    - Goodhart, Arthur L. (Professor) 1958-1967, 3-12
    - Goodrich, Herbert F., Jr., 3-13
      Includes copy of typed manuscript "Climbing the Family Tree" by his father, Judge Herbert F. Goodrich of the U.S. Court of Appeals, Third Circuit.
    - Gordon, Lincoln H. (Professor,; Harvard Business School) 1957, 3-14
    - G-Miscellany (alphabetical), 3-15 to 3-16
      - 3-15, Galbraith, John Kenneth 1963-1964 Garbis, Marvin J. 1971 Gardiner, Rt. Hon. Lord 1966 Garrity, Paul 1967-1968 Gately, John 1969 Gates, Byron E. 1966-1967 Gates, Thomas S. 1959 Georgetown Law Journal 1958 George Washington University, The Law School 1959 Gibson, Cyrus Frank 1965 Gibson, Marion 1955 Giles, Robert 1959-1960 Gillispie, S. Hazard 1966-1969 Glick, David 1962-1963 Goldberg, B. Abbott 1968 Goldfine, Elizabeth 1965
      - 3-16, Goodwin, Procter Hoar 1967 Gorman, Mary H. 1963-1969 Gough, Aidan R. 1967 Gravel, Clarke 1961 Gregory, Arthur H. 1966 Grenier, Julie 1968 Grimes, John S. 1968 Griswold Erwin N. Dean, Harvard Law School; Solicitor-General, U.S. 1965, 1970 Griswold, Harriet (Mrs. E.N. Griswold) Gruener, Midge and Leo 1967
    - Halaby, Najeeb E. 1956-1962, 3-17
    - Hamilton, Fowler 1962, 3-18
    - Hanson, Miles (Reverend) 1964-1967, 3-19
    - Harlan, John Marshall, Justice, U.S. Supreme Court 1958-1970, 3-20
    - Haskins, George L. (Professor) 1960-1969, 3-21
    - Heinz, Elise B. 1960-1965, 3-22
    - Herter, Christian A., Jr. 1958-1960, 3-23
    - Historical Evaluation and Research Organization (HERO) 1956-1971, 4-1 to 4-8
      File relates to numerous studies done by HERO on such things as the:
      Korean Armistice Agreement
      "Guiding and Influencing Asian Armed Forces in Combat"
      "The Neutralization of Vietnam"
      "The Chronology of the American Revolution"
      "A Program to Develop Counterinsurgency Theory"
      "A Proposal to Develop a Total Information System Responsive to the Needs of the Congress of the United States"
      "Disruption in Combat"
      "Documentary History of the Armed Forces of the United States".
      Copy of "A Proposal to Develop a Total Information System Responsive to the Needs of the Congress of the United States"
      Article, "Responding to Disarmament Violations" by Roger Fisher
      Article, "Burma and Its Army: A Contrast in Motivations and Characteristics".
    - H-Miscellany (alphabetical), 5-1 to 5-3
      - 5-1, Haar, Charles 1969 Haberman, Jacob 1969 Haley, Whitney 1962 Hall, Hiland 1967 Hall, Livingston 1958-1969 Hallgring, Robert 1966 Hall of Fame for Great Americans 1969-1970 Halpern, Harold S. 1966 Hammonds, Oliver W. 1964-1967 Hanlon, R. Timothy 1961 Hardee, W. Covington, 1962 Harris, Richard 1968 Harris, William R. 1968 Harrison, Frank 1965-1966 Hartel, Hans 1960 Haskell, Paul 1966-1967
      - 5-2, Hastings, Edwin H. 1958 Hastings, Robert P. 1959-1962 Haviland, John 1969 Hendeman, Deirdre 1957-1959 Henderson, Edith 1971 Henkin, Louis 1967 Henshaw, Weld S. 1967-1968
      - 5-3, Hervey, Thomas G. 1968 Hewitt, Edwin 1965-1966 Hickok, Alan 1965 Hickok, Faith 1962 Hill, Lister 1956-1957 Hird, John W. 1961 Holley, I.B., Jr. 1969 Honerkamp, Rose 1965-1966 Honnold, John 1960 Hope, David 1967 Horner, Henry C. 1960 Horrocks, Brian 1961 Howe, Mark DeWolfe 1964 Howe, Richard R. 1967 Huber, Richard G. 1965 Hutley, F. C. 1958 Hynes, Joseph F. 1965
    - Irani, Phiroze K. 1959, 5-4
    - Jenkins, Elizabeth 1959, 5-5
    - Johanson, Stanley M. 1962-1967, 5-6
    - J-Miscellany (alphabetical), 5-7
      Jacob, Bernard E. 1965
      Janofsky, Leonard S. 1965-1968
      Jayne, Edward R. II 1965
      Jeffreys, David 1960
      Johnson, John A. 1958
      Johnson, Richard B. 1966-1971
      Johnston, John R. 1959
      Jones, Eugene 1964
      Jones, Robert A. 1963
      Jones, Sheldon A. 1959
      Jones, Waldo B. 1960
      Jordan, Raymon 1968
      Juhl, Loren E. 1958
    - Katz, Milton (Professor) 1959, 5-8
    - Kenison, Frank R., Justice,; Supreme Court of New Hampshire, 1961-1970, 5-9
    - Kennedy, Edward F. (U.S. Senator) 1969, 5-10
    - Kennedy, John Fitzgerald (President of the United States) 1959-1966, 5-11 to 5-12
      File relates to WBL's activities as advisor to JFK on defense and military policies during 1959 and 1960. Contains correspondence between the two and memoranda such as "The Unstable Balance of Terror" and "Aspects of Defense Policy for Emphasis".
    - Kennedy, Robert F. (U.S. Senator) 1966-1967, 5-13
    - Kenyon, W. Houston, Jr. 1964-1970, 5-14
    - Kissinger, Henry A. (Professor) 1957-1969, 5-15 to 5-17
      File contains correspondence and a Christmas card from Kissinger to WBL. Also a copy of "The Unsolved Problems of European Defense" by Henry Kissinger and "The Ceylonese Press and the Fall of the Sirimavo Bandaranaike Government" by Raymond E. Vickery, Jr. Much of the early correspondence concerns the Center for International Affairs at Harvard, of which Kissinger was Associate Director and later on Director.
    - Krock, Arthur 1961-1964, 6-1
      File contains correspondence and a statement by the Cuban Judiciary Association (in exile).
    - K-Miscellany (alphabetical), 6-2 to 6-3
      - 6-2, Kalb, Fern E. 1968 Kamine, Bernard S. 1968 Kansas Law Review 1968 Kaplan, Warren K. 1961 Karp, Stephen 1968 Kassoy, David, Paul1964 Katzenbach, Edward L. 1966 Kaufman, H.M. 1962-1965 Kaysen, Carl 1959 Keeffe, Arthur John 1967 Keeton, Robert E. 1968-1970 Keever, Charles J. 1960 Kehoe, William F. 1964 Kelman, Sylvia E. 1970 Kelso, Charles D. 1964 Kennedy, John E. 1959 Kenoff, Jay Stewart 1968 Kent, Glen A. 1962
      - 6-3, Keppel, Francis 1961 Kerivan-Lane Co. 1959-1963 King, Edward C. 1960-1964 Kingsley, G.A. 1964 Kinstlinger, Robert 1967 Kirk, Dewitt B. 1969 Kirschbaum, Elliot A. 1961 Kleinhans, C. Rodney 1959 Knapp, Whitman 1963 Knight, Starr 1965 Knowlton, William A. 1970 Krampf, John 1969 Krieg, William H. 1959 Kunz, David C. 1968 Kunz, Michael 1961
    - Langdale, Noah N., Jr. 1966, 6-4
    - Langenbach, Edward R. 1959-1970, 6-5
    - Leach, Walter Barton: Letters Not Sent 1967, 6-6
    - Leiter, Robert S. 1961, 6-7
    - Levine, Laurence W. 1962-1970, 6-8
    - Little, Brown Company 1957-1971, 6-9 to 6-13
      File relates to WBL's work as a member of the editorial board for Little, Brown's Law Book Department. There is a great deal of correspondence re Professor David Mellinkoff's book Language of the Law and re the possibility of Mellinkoff dditing a legal dictionary. For correspondence with Little, Brown Company re WBL's books, see WRITINGS AND RESEARCH. File contains a copy of the Law School Adoption Report for Little, Brown Company for 1969.
    - Logan, James K. (Dean of the University of Kansas Law School) 1960-1971, 6-14 to 7-2
      For further correspondence with Dean Logan, see WRITINGS AND RESEARCH: Property Law Indicted; Leach and Logan, Cases and Text on Future Interests and Estate Planning, Correspondence; Leach, Cases and Text on the Law of Wills, 2nd Edition, Correspondence.
    - Lusky, Louis (Professor) 1967-1971, 7-3
      File relates to admission of Professor Lusky's son to Harvard College.
    - Lynn, Robert J. (Professor) 1964-1970, 7-4
    - L-Miscellany (alphabetical), 7-5 to 7-7
      - 7-5, Lacovara, Philip P. 1966 Lader, Philip 1971 Laidlaw1960 Lamont, Thomas S. 1967 Landis, James M. 1959 Landwehr, Louise 1966 Lang, Warner W. 1960 Langbein, John H. 1967-1969 Langdon, Hershel G. 1959 Langenbach, Edward Reed, Jr. 1964-1970 Langenbach, R. Randolph 1963 Lanphier, Thomas G. 1960 LaPlante, Joseph A. 1967 Laporte, Cloyd, 1960 Lardner, Lyn 1957 Larsen, Roy E. 1968 Larson, Robert Harlan 1961
      - 7-6, Latta, Cuthber H. 1970 Law Quarterly Review 1967 Lawrence-Toombs, Alfred 1961 Lawson, F.H. 1960 Lawyer, John E., Jr. 1963 Lazerow, Herbert I. 1968 Lee, Duncan C. 1964 Lee, Joel S. 1964-1971 Lee, Lawrence 1965-1969 Leeds, Robert 1959 Leeffe, Arthur J. 1967 Lefcoe, George 1964 Lehrburger, Pauline 1969 LeMay, Curtis E.1966 Lenzner, Terry 1961 LeRoy, L. Neil 1962 Leva, Marx 1965 Levine, Jay H. 1967 Levine, Julius B. 1968 Levine, Robert L. 1965
      - 7-7, Liacos, Paul J. 1970 Libhart, Wayne P. 1961 Liebman, Lance 1970 Lincoln, Freeman 1960 Lincoln's Inn Society 1968-1970 Lindsay, Richard C. 1959 Lodge, Henry Cabot1957 Long Beach Bar Bulletin 1963 Look Magazine 1967 Loss, Margaret Ruth 1969 Lovett, Robert A. 1959 Lowell, James A. 1961 Loyola University, School of Law 1965 Luscombe, Angel 1967 Lynch, S. Arnold 1965-1969
    - McGill University 1961, 7-8
      File relates to speech given by WBL at the McGill Law Banquet 1961.
    - McKee, William F. (General, USAF) 1966-1968, 7-9
    - McNeil, Donald G. 1959-1969, 7-10
    - Massachusetts Board of Bar Examiners 1969, 7-11
    - Mayer-Forster, Mimmi 1955-1963, 7-12
    - Megarry, R.E. 1960-1971, 7-13
      Mr. Megarry was an English barrister and later a judge in the Royal Courts of Justice, London.
    - Mellinkoff, David (Professor) 1962-1968, 7-14
      For further correspondence re Professor Mellinkoff see GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE (UNBOUND): Little, Brown Company, where both Mellinkoff's book Language of the Law and the proposal that he edit a legal dictionary are discussed.
    - Montgomery, Bernard Law (Field Marshal) 1955-1960, 7-15
      File includes typed carbon of WBL's review of Montgomery's Memoirs, published in November 1958.
    - Morris, John H.C. (Professor) 1950-1971 4 folders, 7-16 to 7-19
      Mr. Morris was Professor of Law, Madgalen College, Oxford University, England. Morris and WBL were co-authors of The Rule Against Perpetuities, (1956).
    - M-Miscellany (alphabetical), 8-1 to 8-4
      - 8-1, McCarthy, Barbara Powell 1967 McCaskey, Donald L. 1969 McClennen, Louis 1964 McCloy, John J. 1956 McCone, John A. 1957 McDermott, Robert F. 1958 MacDonald, Joseph A. 1971 McDougal, Myres S. 1967 McGann, Lena C. 1968 McGann, Robert Cox 1971 McGuire, John D. 1968 Machen, Arthur W., Jr. 1959 McKean, Robert E. 1960 McKnight, Joseph W. 1963 McNaughton, John T. 1962-1963 Madden, Robert J. 1971 Magruder, Anita 1968 Maguire, John M. 1962 Mahady, Henry J. 1966 Mailick, Sidney 1968 Mallette, Louis I. 1968 Malone, William 1962 Mannebach, Wayne C. 1961 Mansfield, John H. 1970 Mansfield, J.K. 1959
      - 8-2, Marine Trust 1959 Markey, Howard T. 1959 Marks, Alan D. 1970 Martin, June 1970-1971 Massachusetts Bar Foundation 1967 Massachusetts Trial Lawyers Association 1960 Matloff, Maurice 1959 Maudsley, Ron 1965 Mechem, Philip 1958-1962 Merrill, Charles W. 1965 Meserve, Robert W. 1959-1968
      - 8-3, Metropolitan Life Insurance Company 1965 Michelman, Frank 1967 Miller, Gordon D. 1967-1968 Mississippi Law Institute 1962 Mississippi Law Journal 1964 Mississippi Supreme Court 1962 Moore, Albert 1967 Moran, Joseph H. 1958-1959 Morison, Samuel E. 1958-1963 Morris, Clarence 1965-1967 Morris, Michael 1959 Morrison, C.A. 1969 Morton, Louis 1959 Moss, John J. 1968 Moss, Peyton 1971 Mougey, Frederick K. 1959 Moulton, John K. 1966 Moynihan, Cornelius J. 1962 Moynihan, Daniel P. 1970
      - 8-4, Munn, Cecil E. 1962 Munro, Meredith Vance 1960 Murchison, Charles H. 1966 Murphy, Arthur W. 1967 Murphy, Charles J.V. 1960-1961 Murphy, Edward F. 1968 Murphy, Janet 1967 Murphy, John G., Jr. 1968 Murray, Donald M. 1964 Murray, Herbert F. 1971 Myers, John Sherman 1962-1963
    - Newhall, Guy 1947-1963, 8-5
    - N-Miscellany (alphabetical), 8-6
      Nash, Frank C. 1958-1967
      Navy League 1958
      Nebraska State Bar Association 1960
      Nef, John 1962
      Nelson, Minnie K. 1965
      New England Law Institute, Inc. 1959
      The New Yorker 1963-1967
      New York Law School 1964
      New York Times 1962-1970
      Newbury, Jerry 1958
      Newbury, Samuel P. 1960-1967
      Newbury, Ted and Jack 1959
      Newman, Mortimer G., Jr. 1965
      Newsweek 1968
      Nitze, Paul H. 1967
      Norstad, Lauris 1970
      North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO) 1958
      Northey, J.F. 1967
      Norton, Hugh A. 1963
      Nossaman, Walter L. 1962
      Nufer, H.F. 1965-1966
    - O-Miscellany (alphabetical), 8-7
      Oceana Publications, Inc. 1967
      O'Connell, Jeffrey 1970
      O'Hearn, Charles M. 1959-1961
      Ohio State University, National Security Policy Seminar 1958
      Ohly, John V. 1940
      Orban, Joe 1970
      Ordish, George 1964
      Orlin, Jay E. 1960-1961
      Osmanski, Frank 1959-1964
      Osmond, Donald C. 1958
      Otis, Edward V. 1965-1966
    - Pace, Frank, Jr. 1954-1960, 8-8
      Mr. Pace was Chairman of the Board, General Dynamics Corporation; formerly Secretary of the Army.
    - Parry, Clive (Professor) 1967, 8-9
      Mr. Parry was a professor at Downing College, Cambridge University, England. Folder includes essay by Parry entitled "The British Consular Conventions" (Essays in honor of Lord McNair).
    - Pignatelli, Guido (Prince) 1958-1960, 8-10
    - Platt, Washington (General) 1964-1965, 8-11
    - Powell, Richard R. 1965-1966, 8-12
    - Prentice-Hall, Inc. 1959-1966, 8-13
      File includes correspondence with John G. Powers, President, and contains a copy of "The Prentice-Hall Attorneys' Wills Kit".
    - Price, Don K. (Dean of the Harvard Graduate School of Public Administration) 1958-1967, 8-14
    - Pusey, Nathan M. (President of Harvard University) 1958-1970, 8-15
    - Putnam, Wallace B. 1965-1969, 8-16
      Putnam is an artist and a childhood friend of WBL's.
    - P-Miscellany (alphabetical), 8-17 to 8-18
      - 8-17, Paine, Warren 1959 Palmer, Grant and Mary 1962-1971 Palmer, Walter H. 1966 Pan American World Airways 1969 Pantzer, Kurt F. 1962 Park, David 1968 Pasley, Robert S. 1961-1963 Patterson, L. Ray 1970 Payne, John C. 1967-1968 Paul, Mary L. 1959 Pedrick, Willard H. 1969 Perera, Lawrence T. 1969 Persons, Wilton B. 1958 Philbrick, John W. 1967 Phillips, Asa E., Jr. 1959 Phillips, Thomas R. 1958
      - 8-18, Pi Eta Speakers1971 Pinkerton, William M. 1959 Place, Russell P. 1965-1966 Place, Russell P., Jr. 1961 Plews, John 1959 Plimpton, Francis T.P. 1967 Pollak, Louis H. (Dean,; Yale Law School)1967 Pollock, Edward J. 1959 Posvar, Wesley W. 1969 Potts, Ramsey 1960 Powers, Walter 1969 Preyer, L. Richardson 1959 Prickett, William 1962 Princeton University Press 1959 Proctor, Robert 1958-1961 Prosser, William L. 1959 Putley, James and Sylvia 1966-1967 Putnam, Philip A. 1960-1969
    - Q-Miscellany (alphabetical), 8-19
      Quarles, John R., Jr. 1960
      Quigley, T.B. (Dr.) 1963
      Quinn, William F. (Governor of Hawaii) 1960-1961
    - Righeimer, Frank S., Jr. 1962-1966, 9-1
    - Rodell, Fred (Professor,; Yale Law School) 1962-1967, 9-2
    - Ross, Richard M. 1967-1970, 9-3
      File contains a copy of paper by Ross, "Restrictions on Disinheritance of Illegitimate Ninor Children in California, Florida, Missouri, Nebraska and Washington".
    - R-Miscellany (alphabetical), 9-4 to 9-5
      - 9-4, Rabb, Maxwell M. 1960 Rabin, Edward H. 1965 Radway, Laurence I. 1964 Ralli, Pandia C. 1958-1966 Raymond, Jack 1964 Re, Edward D. 1963 Read, William L. 1958-1961 Reid, David H. 1968 Remington, John W. 1966 Rhyne, Charles S. 1958 Richardson, Charles L. 1958 Richardson, Don 1959 Richardson, Elliot L. 1962-1968 Richardson, John 1968 Richardson, Robert 1965 Rimbach, Sylvia 1966-1968 Robison, Joseph B. 1965 Roby, David M. 1961 Rodriguez, Manuel J. 1968
      - 9-5, Rogers, Eddy J. 1966 Rohan, Patrick J. 1960 Rohrbaugh, Stephen Bunker 1962 The Roscoe Pound-American Trial Lawyers Foundation 1970 Rosenkranz, Milton 1958 Rostow, Eugene 1959-1962 Rostow, Walt W. 1961-1968 Rountree, J. Asa 1961 Rouvelas, Emanuel L. 1968 Rowell, George B. 1960 Rubenstein, Bernard J. 1958 Runge, Carlisle P. 1961-1969 Ruston, Marion 1960 Rutter, Irvin C. 1963 Ryan, Kevin G. 1959-1962
    - Sallagar, Frederick M. 1958-1970, 9-6
      Mr. Sallagar was on the staff of the Rand Corporation for which he wrote a study entitled "The Road to Total War: Escalation in World War II".
    - Saltonstall, John L., Jr. 1964-1971, 9-7
      Mr. Saltonstall was a member of the Boston City Council.
    - Saltonstall, Leverett (U.S. Senator) 1957-1963, 9-8
      File includes photographs of Senator Saltonstall lecturing to the Defense Policy Seminar in December 1975.
    - Schenk, Peter J. 1959-1962, 9-9
    - Schlesinger, Arthur M., Jr. (Professor) 1959-1964, 9-10
      See also GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE (UNBOUND): Schenk, Peter J.
    - Schuyler, Daniel M. 1958-1967, 9-11
      File contains a program for the Institute on Wills and Probate, March 8,9, 1962 at the Southwestern Legal Center in Dallas, Texas.
    - Schwartz, William (Professor) 1961-1967, 9-12
      File contains a copy of Professor Schwartz' pamphlet, Future Interests and Estate Planning; also a typed carbon of WBL's forword to a book on future interests by Professor Schwartz.
    - Scott, Robert L., Jr. (Gerneal, USAF, Retired) 1960-1961, 9-13
    - The Shakespeare-Oxford Society 1959-1966, 9-14 to 9-15
      File relates to the dispute over the "true" author of Shakespeare's works. It contains a copy of "Edward de Vere, The Seventeenth Earl of Oxford: The Real Shakespeare" by William Kent and others.
    - Simes, Lewis M. (Professor of Law,; University of Michigan, later Hastings) 1957-1961, 9-16
    - Slessor, Sir John C. (Marshall of the Royal Air Force) 1958-1970, 9-17 to 9-18
    - Slessor, J.A.F. (son of Sir John Slessor) 1960-1961, 9-19
    - Sloss, Frank H. 1960-1967, 9-20
    - Snider, Donald 1968-1970, 9-21
    - SoundScriber Sales Corporation 1949-1961, 9-22
      File relates to equipment purchased by WBL.
    - Spalding, John V., Associate Justice,; Supreme Judicial Court of Massachusetts, 1958-1969, 10-1
    - Sperm Bank Material 1961-1962, 10-2
    - Stearns, Robert L. 1954-1970, 10-3
    - Sullivan, Rose 1967-1972, 10-4
    - Sundlun, Bruce 1958-1968, 10-5
      File is primarily concerned with attempt in 1960 and 1961 to have Mr. Sundlun appointed as Administrator of the Federal Aviation Agency or for an Air Force Secretariat position.
    - Symington, Stuart (U.S. Senator)1955-1971, 10-6 to 10-10
      File relates mostly to Senator Symington's attempts to unify the three military services and to the possibility of his candidacy for President in 1960. File contains mostly correspondence although there are also press releases and several reports relating to the unification problem; also an address by Senator Symington given in 1955, entitled "The Silent Curtain". Senator Symington was a member of the U.S. Senate Committee on Armed Services and also a member of the Committee on Aeronautical and Space Sciences.
    - S-Miscellany (alphabetical), 10-11 to 10-13
      - 10-11, Sacks, Albert M. 1960-1971 St. Clair, James D. 1962 Salinger, Richard B. 1969 Sarshik, Steven 1971 Schaefer, Walter V. 1967 Schiffer, Winifred 1970 Schoefield, William 1968 Schreiver, Louis 1961 Schroeder, James 1966 Scott, Austin W. 1965-1969 Seavey, Warren A. 1961 Seltzer, Richard S. 1964 Seznec, Simone 1965 Shambaugh, Willard 1968 Sharp, George B. 1963 Shaw, D.P. 1960 Shaw, John D. 1958 Shawmut Bank 1966 Shay, D.E. 1969 Sheard, Gilbert A. 1967 Shedd, Harold W. 1960 Shellow, James 1958 Shepardson, Whitney H. 1962 Sherrill, Dorothy G. 1963-1966 Short, Dean 1970
      - 10-12, Sibley, Alden K. 1964 Sibley, George H. 1969 Simmons, Grant G. 1962 Simonds, Lester O. 1969 Simpson, Albert F. 1958 Singh, R.K. 1966 Slaninger, Frank 1968 Slick, Tom 1960 Smith, Dale O. 1960 Smith, Foster Lee 1962 Smith, Olcott Damon 1967 Smith, Sydney A. 1959 Snodgrass, David E. 1959 Southwestern University Law Review 1970 Spaatz, Carl 1967-1968 Spaeth, Edmund B. 1966 Spaulding, Alice Howard 1962-1966 Speeler, William Earle 1969 Speers, William J. 1959-1961 Spencer, George H. 1961 Spuehler, Don 1964
      - 10-13, Stanford Law Review 1957 Stanley, Timothy W. 1970 Stassen, John H. 1967-1969 Steck, William F. 1961 Stern, Charles W. 1967-1968 Stern, Mike 1969 Stiller, Shale D. 1968 Story, Charles Dale 1959 Stowe, Irving H. 1966 Strait, George 1967 Stratton, Samuel S. 1959 Strausz-Hupe, Robert 1958 Street, Henry Strong, Robert E. 1968 Stumpf, Felix F. 1965-1968 Sturgis, Edward, Jr. 1970 Suffolk University 1958-1970 Sullivan, John L. 1968 Sullivan, Neil 1970 Sultan, Allen 1963 Sutherland, Arthur E. 1963-1970 Sykes, Ethelred L. 1958-1965
    - Tannenwald, Theodore, Jr., Judge,; Tax Court of the U.S., 1959-1968, 11-1
    - Taylor, Telford (Professor) 1959-1967, 11-2
    - Thompson, Samuel L. 1966, 11-3
    - Tuchman, Barbara (author) 1966-1967, 11-4
    - Turrentine, Lowell (Professor of Law,; Stanford University) 1960-1961, 11-5
    - T-Miscellany (alphabetical), 11-6
      Talbott, Harold E. 1957
      Tardiff, Eric H. 1970
      Tarlo, Hyman 1965
      Tarrant, John E. 1967
      Tate, Sally 1971
      Taussig, Joseph K., Jr. 1963
      Taylor, Brown 1959
      Taylor, Lauriston S. 1964
      Taylor, Marvin 1958
      Thornton, Barbara W. 1970
      Thoron, Gray 1962
      Tierney, Paul D. 1968
      Time, Incorporated 1959-1969
      Tischler, Saul 1963
      Todd, Jacob W. 1960-1965
      Toepfer, Louis A. 1968
      The Town Crier ( Wayland, Mass.) 1965
      Trafford, Perry D., Jr. 1965-1966
      Trautman, Herman L. 1967
      Traynor, Roger 1965
      Treat, William W. 1967
      Tredick, Peter W. 1965-1966
      Trevor, Barry 1961
      Trudeau, Arthur G. 1960
      Trynin, Nathan K. 1965-1966
    - University of California, School of Law 1957-1965, 11-7
    - The University of Georgia, School of Law 1968, 11-8
      File relates to a series of lectures WBL was prevented from giving by the severe injury to his hip.
    - University of Pennsylvania Law School:; Hare Law Club 1963, 11-9
    - U-Miscellany (alphabetical), 11-10
      United States Army Artillery and Missile School 1967
      United States Bureau of Customs, Boston, Mass. 1969
      University of California, Los Angeles 1968
      University of Colorado, School of Law 1958
      University of Detroit 1968
      University of Michigan Press 1960
    - V-Miscellany (alphabetical), 11-11
      van Bibber, Julia 1959
      Vandam, Leory D. 1958
      Van Dyke, Jon M. 1968
      Villanova Law Review1963
      Vogt, Edward L. 1962
      Volpe, John A. 1967
      Vom Baur, F. Trowbridge 1960
      Vorenberg, James 1971
    - Walkowicz, T.F. 1957, 11-12
      File contains a draft and a finished copy of "Survival In an Age of Technological Contest".
    - Wasson, Peter 1959, 11-13
    - Waterbury, Thomas L. (Professor of Law,; University of Minnesota) 1957-1961, 11-14
    - Waterhouse, James F. 1955-1968, 11-15
    - West Publishing Company 1959-1971, 11-16
    - Westfall, David (Professor,; Harvard Law School) 1967-1969, 11-17
    - White, Byron R., Associate Justice,; United States Supreme Court, 1961-1965, 11-18
    - Wilkins, Raymond S., Chief Justice, Supreme Judicial Court of Massachusetts, 1959-1961, 11-19
    - Wolfe, Albert B. 1957-1967, 11-20
      File contains copies of a report to the American Bar Association on "The Improvement of Conveyancing and Recording Practices" and drafts for an Act in Massachusetts, "To Protect Land Titles From Uncertain and Obsolete Restrictions".
    - Wyzanski, Charles E., Jr., Chief Justice, United States District Court, 1965-1966, 11-21
      File contains a xeroxed copy of a rough draft of "Trial and Error: Reflections of a United States District Judge".
    - W-Miscellany (alphabetical), 11-22 to 11-23